

PHAN MINH PHUONG TRINH

Contact

- +84935 153 274
- trinhph47@gmail.com
- Vu Huu st., Hai Chau district, Danang city

Education

2013 - 2017

Bachelors Degree, **Business Administration** University of Economics, Danang

Strengths

Critical Thinking

Problem Solving

Communication

Time Management

Skills

MS Office

English

About

As an adaptable and a solution-oriented person, I always work hard to achieve the best result in the workplace. Having worked as a fulfillment in e-Commerce company for 2 years helps me being excellent in working with others to achieve a certain objective on time and at the highest level. I enjoy overcoming challenges and seek to expand career growth to management.

Work Experience

Fulfillment Manager

2018 - 2020 Bubble Style, Danang

- Reading and dispensing workloads to others.
- Receiving and fulfilling daily orders in a timely, efficient manner.
- Reviewing purchasing agreements with vendors and maintain strong open lines of communications with those vendors.
- Developing an active process for measuring supply inventory and determining purchasing needs based on quarterly and annual sales.
- Comparing product deliveries with issued orders and contacting vendors when there are discrepancies.
- Establishing long-term purchasing arrangements with vendors when it is beneficial to the organization.

Casual Purchasing Accountant

2017

Paris Deli Hotel, Danang

- Handling administrative duties relating to purchases, including tracking orders and ensuring records are kept up to date.
- Coordinating the daily purchase of products and materials by checking and guaranteeing the quality and quantity of the daily use products.

Promotion Team Leader

2016-2017 AIESEC Danang

- Presenting and communicating the Global Volunteer Program AIESEC to the youngsters.
- Creating and maintaining events that educated, informed and drawn people to the Global Volunteer program.